boyreview.com 2012-12-26

# Your privacy is important to us, and even more important to you, so kindly read this.

## PRIVACY

BoyReview.com respects your privacy. This policy explains how BoyReview.com will treat information that it may obtain from you as you make use of the BoyReview.com site. The owners and operators of BoyReview.com ("BoyReview.com") provide the BoyReview.com site ("Site") subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may change from time to time, without notice other than appearing on the Site. The Revision Date below will show you when the Privacy Policy was last revised.

## The BoyReview.com Site and Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the BoyReview.com Site. The Site may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by BoyReview.com. BoyReview.com has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party website. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party websites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release BoyReview.com from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party website to which this Site may be linked.

## Information Collected on this Site

When you visit the Site, we may collect passive information about your visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data, or historical data. It may include the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g., whether you logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the Site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform). We use this information to track how users are accessing and using the Site.

In addition, when you visit the Site we generally collect the IP Address of the computer you are using to access the Site. (An IP, or "Internet Protocol," address is a unique number associated with your computer, that may be communicated to other computers and servers when you use the Internet.) We use this information for purposes of security and anti-fraud protection.

BoyReview.com also uses cookies and/or web beacons. (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, and that may be accessed when you use a website. A web beacon is a small, transparent graphic image placed on a website, which allows the site to record the actions of a visitor opening the page that contains the beacon.)

We may use cookies or web beacons to: (1) determine whether visitors to the Site are unique, or whether the same user is visiting the site on multiple occassions; (2) help deliver advertisements; (3) track usage throughout the Site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Site, etc.); (4) store your agreement to the terms and conditions for entering and using the Site; (5) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

These kinds of information do not, on their own, personally identify you. However, they can potentially be combined with information obtained from other sources in order to identify you. BoyReview.com does not ordinarily seek or obtain personally identifying information about users from others. It does reserve the right to seek such information in the event of a violation of the BoyReview.com Terms of Service, in the event of a dispute between BoyReview.com and you, or if required by law to do so.

## Content You Submit to or Post on the Site

BoyReview.com allows you to submit and post audio and video content, and accompanying text ("User Content"). User Content that you submit to BoyReview.com or post on the Site, including any personal information included in your User Content, becomes publicly available and can be seen, collected, and used by others. You should not post any content on the Site that you do not want to be seen, collected, or used by others. 

In the process of posting User Content, you may be asked to provide some personally identifying information, such as your name, address, and e-mail address, and other documentation. We will keep a record of the information you provide, including your personally identifiable information, and that information will be linked in our records to the User Content. We will not publically post your name or other personally identifying information, and we will not provide such information to our advertisers or business partners without your permission. However, we may disclose the personally identifying information and documentation you provide in some limited circumstances, as set forth below ("Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information").

## Use of Visitor Information Collected on the Site

We do not collect or share personally identifiable information about visitors to the site through the ordinary operation of the Site. We may obtain and merge information about users and usage of the Site into aggregated data, which may then be used by us and/or shared with advertisers or others. When we provide aggregated information to outside companies, they will not be able to identify you or contact you based on that data. 

## Usage Information - Collection and Use by Advertisers and Others

BoyReview.com allows other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is important to us. We do not knowingly allow children to use the Site, and all visitors to the Site must confirm that they are at least 21 years old. We do not collect or maintain information at our Web sites from those we actually know are under 21, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 21.

## Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information

BoyReview.com generally does not collect personally identifiable information (data such as your name, email address, password, and the content of your communications) unless you submit User Content for posting on the Site. BoyReview.com will not disclose any personally identifiable information it collects or obtains except: (1) as described in the BoyReview.com Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy; (2) after obtaining your permission to a specific use or disclosure; (3) if BoyReview.com is required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement); (4) as required to protect BoyReview.com's property, safety, or operations, or the property or safety of others; or (5) as otherwise required by law.

## Security

Some pages of the Site may use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information that is transmitted through the Site. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.

## Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about BoyReview.com's Privacy Policy and use of personal information, please contact us using our contact form.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on 20th of August 2011.
